<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!--
account.xml
tjs 100115

file version 1.00 

release version 1.15
template used for basic Job Cost Quotations
Modify this file for each Collaborator Account that is established.
-->
<account id="6">
<last>
Tester
</last>
<first>
Tessie
</first>
<name>
Test Us Construction
</name>
<tagline>
Hire The Three HouseTesters For All House Repairs!
</tagline>
<street1>
444 Loverly Lane
</street1>
<city>
Lynn
</city>
<state>
MA
</state>
<zip>
01905
</zip>
<phones>
<phone type="main">
1-800-555-1212
</phone>
<phone type="mobile">
1-800-444-1212
</phone>
</phones>
<emails>
<email>
testConstruction@AOL.com
</email>
</emails>
<url>
</url>
<policies>
<policy type="About Test Us:">
<bullet>
Fully insured throughout New England
</bullet>
<bullet>
License #123456
</bullet>
<bullet>
Member: Contractors' Collaborative Logistics Management Group (www.collogistics.com)
</bullet>
<bullet>
When contacted we can provide referrals from satisfied customers.
</bullet>
</policy>
<policy type="Terms:">
<bullet>
Free estimates throughout New England
</bullet>
<bullet>
Quotations for jobs are made in good faith based upon customers' requirements.  The amounts cited are subject to change after 30 days. Changes could occur if requirements are changed and/or unexpected, unforeseen problems arise during construction.
</bullet>
<bullet>
Please contact us if there are any questions about this proposal or to setup a schedule when work can begin.
</bullet>
<bullet>
We use quality material that comes with manufacturers' warantees.  In addition our standard quality assurance workmanship warantee is for 1 year.
</bullet>
<bullet>
We cannot discuss specific job schedules until we plan a meeting to accept this proposal.  In general our payment policy is to receive one third payment upon proposal and schedule acceptance, one third payment when the construction is half completed, and one third payment within thirty days of job's completion and customer acceptance.
</bullet>
</policy>
</policies>
</account>
